• We had real fun doing this project. The journey was challenging and sometimes nerve wracking too. Starting from step 1, that is from scraping  the dataset, the main challenge was, getting our IPs blocked. Around 23 IPs were blocked in total (We resetting private IP and using VPNs from different locations in USA) But still we ended up getting our IP's blocked and ended up with the "human captcha" page which our bot couldn't get through.
• In the end, it was a very good learning experience and got to know how smart the indeed.com website in preventing web scrappers such as changing the locations of tags in different pages and redirecting the job description to different tab sometimes.
• We were able to some what fool the system up to an extent by closing and reopening the chrome driver (continuing in the same url) so that the browser cookies and cache is deleted.



